<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Something on The Rod Serling Memorial Foundation</title>
    <link>your%20site%20url/categories/something/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Something on The Rod Serling Memorial Foundation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2015 rsmf</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 19:47:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="your%20site%20url/categories/something/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>/your%20site%20url/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 19:47:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/your%20site%20url/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Rod Serling&amp;rsquo;s achievements in playwriting, speech making and broadcasting are considerable and important. As members of The Rod Serling Memorial Foundation, we dedicate ourselves to promote and preserve this great man&amp;rsquo;s contributions to the Arts and Humanities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We pledge to educate the public about Rod Serling&amp;rsquo;s genius and his passion, hoping that they will understand and appreciate his mastery of the creative arts, his unique understanding of human relationships, his esteem as a writer, his generosity as a speaker in and around Binghamton, and his uncompromising commitment to quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-founding-of-the-rod-serling-memorial-foundation:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;The Founding of the Rod Serling Memorial Foundation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were several attempts to memorialize Rod Serling following his death. Don Snyder, former general manager of WNBF-TV, in editorial on two different occasions, urged the community to remember Rod Serling in some significant manner. Through a well-received 1981 documentary entitled &amp;ldquo;Rod Serling: Remembered&amp;rdquo; on WMGC-TV, news anchor Julie Ross spurred public interest with a suggestion that Recreation Park or the high school might be named after Rod. On June 11th, 1983, Mayor Juanita Crabb and the Binghamton Local Development Corporation made possible the world premiere of &amp;ldquo;Twilight Zone The Movie&amp;rdquo; at the Crest Theatre in Binghamton New York.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;in-february-1985-the-rod-serling-memorial-committee-was-formed-the-founders:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;In February 1985, the Rod Serling Memorial Committee was formed. The founders:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;David G. Stearns, Chairperson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stanley G. Gilinsky, Vice Chairperson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charles Lesko, Jr., Treasurer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ethel F. Molessa, Secretary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helen M. Foley, Creative Director&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carol Serling, Advisor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jem Aswad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helen Bailey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;William Behan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mare A. Ferro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael T. Fuir&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bill Foley&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Betsy Aswad&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Barbara Furch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Richard N. Aswad  Yvonne Gabel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sybil Goldenberg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eileen Haley&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;M. Joan Handy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anne Greiner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Norma F. Lawson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruthe B. Lee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jules Levitt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lonna McKeon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ann E. McNulty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Irene McNulty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;R.D. Rosenbaum&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phyllis Stearns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shirley Weinstein&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the fall of 1986, the Committee became the ROD SERLING FOUNDATION and was later recognized as a non-profit, tax exempt organization in 1987.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AT RIGHT:
Sybil Goldenberg, Foundation Board Member, posing with a portion of our film archive. 1989. Source: New York Times&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>